<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Battle of the Beards</title>
    <link>http://battleofthebeards.info/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Battle of the Beards</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 18:08:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://battleofthebeards.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Gadget Jumble</title>
      <link>http://battleofthebeards.info/gadgetJumble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 18:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://battleofthebeards.info/gadgetJumble/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;As part of our day of beardy fun, we&amp;rsquo;re hoping that all the attending beards will bring along unwanted tech for a gadget jumble&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-brief&#34;&gt;In Brief&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To help raise more money for CALM, we&amp;rsquo;d like to be able to sell on unwanted tech from the beards who are attending&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-whole-nine-yards&#34;&gt;The Whole Nine Yards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any unwanted tech gadgets that you&amp;rsquo;d like to see go to a grateful home, or to be cannibalised into some world dominating techno-beast, then bring them along!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;d like to take the opportunity to help you de-clutter your man (or woman) caves of those pieces of tech that you still haven&amp;rsquo;t found a use for, even after all this time.
Come on, you now you had a good reason for buying that veeblefetzer to interface to the doohickey, but you never have the time do you?
Make a clean break with all your (useable and functional) detritus and use it to raise money for this great cause, with all money raised from the sales will go to the supported charity.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget though, even if you&amp;rsquo;ve donated items, you can still buy other shiny-shiny tech from our helpful volunteers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All we ask is that items are NOT in a dangerous state and that the lucky purchasers don&amp;rsquo;t expect any kind of warrantee. Donations accepted on the day at the Bierkeller and you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to purchase throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battle of the Beards History</title>
      <link>http://battleofthebeards.info/AboutEvents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 16:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://battleofthebeards.info/AboutEvents/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Battle of the Beards started out as a fun user group event, where bristling techies would square off in our very own arena. Our Beardy Battlers would give presentations and winners would be decided based on the quality of their beards and their talks.
The crowd went wild (and wanted more)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where our first events had a mere 3 contenders, this year we&amp;rsquo;re upping the ante and there&amp;rsquo;ll be at least 10 contenders! Whether their beard is permanent or just for the day, our Beardy Battlers will be delivering half-hour techie talks that&amp;rsquo;ll be useful and engaging for anyone in IT. Every Beardy Battler will make a difference to your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you come along you&amp;rsquo;ll make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll make a difference in the room and to somebody you may never meet. That&amp;rsquo;s because, after we&amp;rsquo;ve covered the costs, all proceeds will go to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thecalmzone.net/&#34;&gt;Campaign Against Living Miserably (CALM)&lt;/a&gt;.
Supporting CALM means they can provide vital counselling services and save lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our male dominated industry, we’re likely to be disproportionately affected by suicide. It was the cause of a quarter of all deaths of 20 - 34 year old males in &lt;a href=&#34;http://webarchive.nationalarchives.gov.uk/20160105160709/http://www.ons.gov.uk/ons/rel/vsob1/mortality-statistics--deaths-registered-in-england-and-wales--series-dr-/2014/sty-what-do-we-die-from.html&#34;&gt;2014&lt;/a&gt;.
That&amp;rsquo;s a sad and uncomfortable fact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need to take care of ourselves and each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So let’s have some fun for a good cause!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://battleofthebeards.info/codeofconduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 16:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://battleofthebeards.info/codeofconduct/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking to have a fun and admittedly kind of blokey conference aimed at helping tackle a big issue - male suicide. Our organising committee is of mixed genders and aims to make a conference everyone is welcome at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-quick-version&#34;&gt;The Quick Version&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our conference is dedicated to providing a harassment-free conference experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of conference participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any conference venue, including talks, workshops, parties, Twitter and other online media. Conference participants violating these rules may be sanctioned or expelled from the conference without a refund at the discretion of the conference organisers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-less-quick-version&#34;&gt;The Less Quick Version&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harassment includes offensive verbal comments related to gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion, technology choices, sexual images in public spaces, deliberate intimidation, stalking, following, harassing photography or recording, sustained disruption of talks or other events, inappropriate physical contact, and unwelcome sexual attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participants asked to stop any harassing behavior are expected to comply immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sponsors are also subject to the anti-harassment policy. In particular, sponsors should not use sexualised images, activities, or other material. Booth staff (including volunteers) should not use sexualised clothing/uniforms/costumes, or otherwise create a sexualised environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a participant engages in harassing behavior, the conference organisers may take any action they deem appropriate, including warning the offender or expulsion from the conference with no refund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are being harassed, notice that someone else is being harassed, or have any other concerns, please contact a member of conference staff immediately. Conference staff can be identified as they&amp;rsquo;ll be wearing branded clothing and/or badges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conference staff will be happy to help participants contact hotel/venue security or local law enforcement, provide escorts, or otherwise assist those experiencing harassment to feel safe for the duration of the conference. We value your attendance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We expect participants to follow these rules at conference and workshop venues and conference-related social events.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>